<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<languages>
  <language name="English" id="en">
    <Commerce>
      <Checkout>
        <Openpay>
			<PaymentNotSpecified>Payment information is not specified.</PaymentNotSpecified>
			<ProcessPaymentNullHttpContext>HttpContext.Current is null.</ProcessPaymentNullHttpContext>
			<PaymentNotAssociatedOrderForm>Payment must be associated with an order form.</PaymentNotAssociatedOrderForm>
			<OpenpaySettingsError>Error in Openpay Payment settings. Please contact site's administrator.</OpenpaySettingsError>
			<InvalidCustomerInfo> Billing or Shipping address are lacking of info. Please make sure to fill in Line1, City, Region and PostalCode.</InvalidCustomerInfo>
			<CheckoutProcessError> Payment transaction cannot be completed.  Please contact site's administrator.</CheckoutProcessError>
			<CancelMessage> Openpay transaction was cancelled.</CancelMessage>
			<FailureMessage> There's some failures occur during the Openpay payment process.</FailureMessage>
			<PaymentCaptureError> There's some failures occur during the Openpay capture payment process.</PaymentCaptureError>
			<PlanPurchasePriceCompareError> There's some failures occur during the comparision payment information with Openpay.</PlanPurchasePriceCompareError>
			<EpiCreateCaptureTransactionError> Your order have created successfully but some errors occur in capture order. Please contact site's administrator about this notification !</EpiCreateCaptureTransactionError>
			<ProcessPaymentStatusCompleted> This order has already paid in Openpay Payment.</ProcessPaymentStatusCompleted>
			<InvalidPurchasePrice> The total price is out of the purchase minimum or maximum limitation of Openpay Payment.</InvalidPurchasePrice>
			<IncludeProhibitedProduct> This order include products prohibited by Openpay Payment policy.</IncludeProhibitedProduct>
			<OpenpayRefundError> Errors occurred. Refund transaction cannot be completed.</OpenpayRefundError>
			<RefundMoreThanPurchasePrice> New Purchase Price is greater than current Purchase Price.</RefundMoreThanPurchasePrice>
			<GetOrderStatusApiError> Cannot get order status from Openpay API.</GetOrderStatusApiError>
			<NotEnoughStockWarning> Payment completed but not enough stock. Please contact administrators.</NotEnoughStockWarning>
			<CartValidationWarning> An error occurred when processing cart.</CartValidationWarning>
			<PlanStatusIsNotActive> Openpay plan must be Active for this feature to apply.</PlanStatusIsNotActive>
        </Openpay>
      </Checkout>
    </Commerce>
  </language>
</languages>